lahorimela.com 2009-11-26

# ..::LahoriMela.com::.. Privacy and Policy

| 

..::LaHoRiMeLa.cOm::.. Free Chat, Shugal Mela Forums, Free Wallpapers Pakistani Songs, Free SMS, Free Jokes, Pakistani Recipes, Cook Book, Free Online Tv, Free Online Videos, Daily Horoscope, Send Lovely Greeting Cards And Lots More 

|   
---  
|   |  | 

**  Lahori Kartutein**  
  
---  
  
..::LaHoRiMeLa.cOm::.. Free Chat, Shugal Mela Forums, Free Wallpapers Pakistani Songs, Free SMS, Free Jokes, Pakistani Recipes, Cook Book, Free Online Tv, Free Online Videos, Daily Horoscope, Send Lovely Greeting Cards And Lots More 

---  
  
**  Total Hits  
**  

| 

If you need more information about **LaHoRiMeLa.cOm** , Please **Contact Us**  
Any personal information you (”You”/”Member”) give us is treated confidentially and held with care and security. 

Please read the following statement to understand how we use your personal information. This policy may change from time to time so please check back on a regular basis.

 **How we gather information:**  
We will NEVER release your personal information to any other third party without your express permission except for the sole purpose of data verification and supplementation. When we give information to the advertisers, agencies or other companies that participate in the Service, it is in the form of grouped statistics based on members’ information while participating in the Service. The Service is designed to make it impossible for outside companies to extract personal information without your consent. We follow rigorous security protocols within our company to safeguard any personal information you share with us.

**How We Use Information:**  
The personal information you provide is used to customize the Service to your needs. For example, if you select cinema and music as interests, only advertisers with promotions relevant to these interests will be interested in sending you any information on their offering or events.  
Advertising partners will be able to plan marketing campaigns using aggregate profile data. For example, they could choose to send a promotion to all users of the Service living in Dubai, interested in music and arts. However, they will not be able to access any individual profile data unless you’ve stated so.  
We may do research and provide reports on our users’ demographics, interests and behavior based on the information provided to us upon registration. This research and reports only relates to groups in general and will never identify you individually. We may share these general statistics with advertisers or partners to enable them to better provide advertisements or offers to members in their areas of interest.

**How We Share Information:**  
We do not sell or rent your information to anyone. Your personal information will not be released to any third party without your express permission except in special circumstances such as when the law requires it or under the circumstances described below.  
Some advertisements or promotions sent to you as part of the Service may contain options to interact with the sender (e.g. a call back function or a link to a Web site). When you provide information while visiting partner sites, it’s the partner site that collects your personal information. The information practices of these partner companies, advertisers and web sites linked to the **LaHoRiMeLa.cOm** Service are not covered by this privacy statement. Please note that the privacy policies of partner sites may differ from those of the Service. We may share our group statistical research and reports with advertisers or partner  
In the event that this business is sold or integrated with another business your details may be disclosed to our advisers and any prospective purchaser’s advisers and will be passed on to the new owners of the business.

**Changing, Correcting and Updating Information:**  
Members opt-in to receive advertisements and promotions at registration. At any time, you may adjust messages received by updating your personal profile in the Profile section on the website.  
You can opt-in to receive promotions or offers from advertisers and partners via several technical platforms (e.g. Email, Web). At any time during participation in the Service, you can enable or disable any such platform by updating your personal profile in the Profile section on the Service website.  
Member Choices For Use Of Information  
Members can update their own personal account information at any time by updating their personal profile in the Profile section on the Service website.  
Consent  
By disclosing your personal information on the Service web site, you consent to the collection, storage and processing of your personal information by the Service in the manner set out in this privacy statement.

**LaHoRiMeLa.cOm** reserves the right to change this Statement, and/or any part thereof, at any time. Any change to the Statement shall be effective upon posting the modified Statement on the Service web site under Privacy Statement and **LaHoRiMeLa.cOm** notifying the posting of the modified agreement on the Service web page for a period of 30 days. Member’s non-termination or continued use of Service after this period shall be deemed acceptance of the modified Statement.  
Advertisers  
We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.

**External Links:**  
This site contains links to other sites. **LaHoRiMeLa.cOm** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.  
Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can **Contact Us**

|    
  | 

LaHoRiMeLa.cOm Free Chat, Shugal Mela Forums, Free Wallpapers Pakistani Songs, Free SMS, Free Jokes, Pakistani Recipes, Cook Book, Free Online Tv, Free Online Videos, Daily Horoscope, Send Lovely Greeting Cards And Lots More. Its all about Lahore Da Mela  Online Users

Copyright 2006 [LahoriMela.com](http://lahorimela.com/). All Rights are Reserved.

Best Viewed at 800 X 600 Resolutions

|
